urpad.net 2014-02-09

# URPad | Privacy Policy

## Web Hosting Plans

  * Stable & Reliable Servers  
URPad.net utilizes powerful, high performance Intel Dual Xeon processors for maximum performance. At URPad, we never compromise on quality.
  * 99.9% Uptime Guarantee!  
URPad.net guarantees a 99.9% uptime with all shared, reseller, and VPS services.
  * 24/7 Support  
URPad provides US based support technicians ready to assist you, day or night 24/7 every day of the year.

## URPad Features

  * Free Website Transfer
  * 24x7x365 US Support
  * Instant Setup
  * RAID Storage
  * POP, Imap Support
  * Top Notch Services
  * Premium Network
  * 99.9% Uptime Guarantee
  * NO Contracts
  * NO Hidden Charges
  * Secure Servers 
  * Server Monitoring

## URPad.net Privacy Policy

URPad.net has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site.

**Information Automatically Logged**

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. We use this information for no other reason.

**Order Forms**

Our site uses an order form for customers to request services. (128 bit encryption). We collect sensitive information which is used only for our purpose, not third party receives any type of information from us.

Contact information from the order forms is used to get in touch with the customer when necessary.

Billing information that is collected is used to bill the user for services.

Unique identifiers are collected from Web site visitors to verify the user's identity.

Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site.

We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences.

**Security**

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. We use strong SSL encryption to ensure your privacy.

**Third Parties**

Information collected on this site is strictly for our use, NO OTHER OUTSIDE PERSONS MAY VIEW YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION SUCH BILLING INFORMATION, ETC.

**Contacting the Web Site**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact: admin@urpad.net
